YAHOR LABANAU

Software Testing Engineer











(25) +375 (25) 534-34-40

WORK EXPERIENCE

1) Software Testing Enginner

EPAM Systems (08/2023 - now)

Employee Feedback Portal (Internal Web Application)

2) Software Testing Enginner

EPAM Systems (04/2023 - 08/2023)

Employee 1-2-1 Evaluation Module

(part of Internal Employee Feeback Portal Web

Application)

3) Junior / Middle Software Testing Enginner

EPAM Systems (12/2020 - 04/2022)

Learning Portal (Web Application)

4) Trainee Software Testing Enginner

EPAM Systems (10/2020 - 12/2020)

Belarusian Volleyball Federation

(Training Web Application)

TECHNOLOGIES & SKILLS

SUMMARY

 Software Testing Engineer with ~2 years of experience in manual web testing looking for a Remote job or Relocation opportunities.

· Will make a great addition to any team due to being proactive and

• Currently, learning Automation in Java to become a Full-stack QA

Engineer so that I could be more involved in the SDLC by writing auto-tests on the manually documented the test-cases and

· Looking forward to new opportunities and possibilities to improve

the delivery success of the projects I'm going to contribute to.

- Functional/Non-Functional requirements analysis before writing checklists for each story
- Identification of the issues' priority, severity, influence on the related functionality

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Developing and maintaining test documentation (test-cases, checklists, bug reports, test result reports)
- Test-cases' peer review
- Communication with customers and team members
- Demo sessions for team members and customers
- Working according to common Agile (SCRUM) workflow and participating in common events (backlog refinement, planning, estimations, daily-scrum, retrospective, etc.)
- Support releases
- Onboarding new team members and mentoring junior testers
- Build deployment
- Web services and API testing
- Validating data in databases
 - _____

EDUCATION

2016 - 2021

Minsk State Linguistic University

Diploma

Linguistics, Regional Geography, Pedagogy

08/2023 - in progress

RedRover QA Automation School (Stream 7)

10/2021 - 01/2022

EPAM JavaScript for Software Testing Engineers Program

08/2021 - 11/2021

EPAM Functional Testing Mentoring Program (Basic)

04/2022 - 04/2023 Compulsory Military Service (Belarus) Manual Testing **

willing to learn.

Experienced in:

· GUI testing

API testing

· Functional testing

Regression testingIntegration testing

· Compatibility testing

Requirements analysisTest-cases development

· Defect management

· Exploratory testing

· Pairwise testing

reviewing those of others.

- SQL **
- NoSQL ★
- API ☆
- Git (GitLab) *
- UML ☆
- Java 8 ★
- JavaScript ★
- HTML ☆
- CSS ★
- HTTP(S) ★
- TCP/IP ★
- Agile (Scrum) **

- Jira **
- MSSQL ★
- PostgreSQL *
- TestLink **
- VS Code *
- IntelliJ IDEA ★
- SoapUI *
- Postman ★
- Swagger *
- SOAP ★
- REST ★
- Jenkins ★

LANGUAGES

Belorussian (Native)

Russian (Native)

English (C1)Spanish (B2)

Polish (A1)